(this.webpackJsonpquizapp=this.webpackJsonpquizapp||[]).push([[0],{34:function(e,t,a){e.exports=a(45)},39:function(e){e.exports=JSON.parse('[{"category":"Entertainment%3A%20Video%20Games","type":"multiple","difficulty":"hard","question":"What%20was%20the%20name%20of%20the%20hero%20in%20the%2080s%20animated%20video%20game%20%27Dragon%27s%20Lair%27%3F","correct_answer":"Dirk%20the%20Daring","incorrect_answers":["Arthur","Sir%20Toby%20Belch","Guy%20of%20Gisbourne"]},{"category":"Animals","type":"multiple","difficulty":"easy","question":"What%20is%20the%20scientific%20name%20for%20modern%20day%20humans%3F","correct_answer":"Homo%20Sapiens","incorrect_answers":["Homo%20Ergaster","Homo%20Erectus","Homo%20Neanderthalensis"]},{"category":"Entertainment%3A%20Books","type":"multiple","difficulty":"hard","question":"What%20is%20Ron%20Weasley%27s%20middle%20name%3F","correct_answer":"Bilius","incorrect_answers":["Arthur","John","Dominic"]},{"category":"Entertainment%3A%20Comics","type":"multiple","difficulty":"easy","question":"Who%20is%20the%20creator%20of%20the%20comic%20series%20%22The%20Walking%20Dead%22%3F","correct_answer":"Robert%20Kirkman","incorrect_answers":["Stan%20Lee","Malcolm%20Wheeler-Nicholson","Robert%20Crumb"]},{"category":"Entertainment%3A%20Board%20Games","type":"multiple","difficulty":"medium","question":"At%20the%20start%20of%20a%20standard%20game%20of%20the%20Monopoly%2C%20if%20you%20throw%20a%20double%20six%2C%20which%20square%20would%20you%20land%20on%3F","correct_answer":"Electric%20Company","incorrect_answers":["Water%20Works","Chance","Community%20Chest"]},{"category":"Geography","type":"multiple","difficulty":"easy","question":"What%20is%20the%20capital%20of%20Jamaica%3F","correct_answer":"Kingston","incorrect_answers":["Rio%20de%20Janeiro","Dar%20es%20Salaam","Kano"]},{"category":"History","type":"multiple","difficulty":"medium","question":"When%20did%20Jamaica%20recieve%20its%20independence%20from%20England%3F%20","correct_answer":"1962","incorrect_answers":["1492","1963","1987"]},{"category":"Animals","type":"boolean","difficulty":"easy","question":"Kangaroos%20keep%20food%20in%20their%20pouches%20next%20to%20their%20children.","correct_answer":"False","incorrect_answers":["True"]},{"category":"General%20Knowledge","type":"multiple","difficulty":"medium","question":"In%202013%20how%20much%20money%20was%20lost%20by%20Nigerian%20scams%3F","correct_answer":"%2412.7%20Billion","incorrect_answers":["%2495%20Million","%24956%20Million","%242.7%20Billion"]},{"category":"History","type":"multiple","difficulty":"medium","question":"How%20old%20was%20Lyndon%20B.%20Johnson%20when%20he%20assumed%20the%20role%20of%20President%20of%20the%20United%20States%3F","correct_answer":"55","incorrect_answers":["50","60","54"]},{"category":"Entertainment%3A%20Video%20Games","type":"multiple","difficulty":"hard","question":"In%20World%20of%20Warcraft%20lore%2C%20who%20organized%20the%20creation%20of%20the%20Paladins%3F","correct_answer":"Alonsus%20Faol","incorrect_answers":["Uther%20the%20Lightbringer","Alexandros%20Mograine","Sargeras%2C%20The%20Daemon%20Lord"]},{"category":"Entertainment%3A%20Video%20Games","type":"boolean","difficulty":"medium","question":"In%20the%20game%20%22Subnautica%22%2C%20a%20%22Cave%20Crawler%22%20will%20attack%20you.","correct_answer":"True","incorrect_answers":["False"]},{"category":"Entertainment%3A%20Japanese%20Anime%20%26%20Manga","type":"multiple","difficulty":"medium","question":"What%20is%20the%20name%20of%20the%20device%20that%20allows%20for%20infinite%20energy%20in%20the%20anime%20%22Dimension%20W%22%3F","correct_answer":"Coils","incorrect_answers":["Wires","Collectors","Tesla"]},{"category":"Entertainment%3A%20Video%20Games","type":"multiple","difficulty":"medium","question":"What%20is%20the%20name%20of%20Cream%20the%20Rabbit%27s%20mom%20in%20the%20%22Sonic%20the%20Hedgehog%22%20series%3F","correct_answer":"Vanilla","incorrect_answers":["Peach","Strawberry","Mint"]},{"category":"History","type":"multiple","difficulty":"easy","question":"These%20two%20countries%20held%20a%20commonwealth%20from%20the%2016th%20to%2018th%20century.","correct_answer":"Poland%20and%20Lithuania","incorrect_answers":["Hutu%20and%20Rwanda","North%20Korea%20and%20South%20Korea","Bangladesh%20and%20Bhutan"]},{"category":"Entertainment%3A%20Television","type":"multiple","difficulty":"hard","question":"Which%20of%20these%20voices%20wasn%27t%20a%20choice%20for%20the%20House%20AI%20in%20%22The%20Simpsons%20Treehouse%20of%20Horror%22%20short%2C%20House%20of%20Whacks%3F","correct_answer":"George%20Clooney","incorrect_answers":["Matthew%20Perry","Dennis%20Miller","Pierce%20Brosnan"]},{"category":"Entertainment%3A%20Music","type":"multiple","difficulty":"medium","question":"From%20which%20album%20is%20the%20Gorillaz%20song%2C%20%22On%20Melancholy%20Hill%22%20featured%20in%3F","correct_answer":"Plastic%20Beach","incorrect_answers":["Demon%20Days","Humanz","The%20Fall"]},{"category":"General%20Knowledge","type":"boolean","difficulty":"easy","question":"Scotland%20voted%20to%20become%20an%20independent%20country%20during%20the%20referendum%20from%20September%202014.","correct_answer":"False","incorrect_answers":["True"]},{"category":"Entertainment%3A%20Video%20Games","type":"multiple","difficulty":"medium","question":"In%20Left%204%20Dead%2C%20which%20campaign%20has%20the%20protagonists%20going%20through%20a%20subway%20in%20order%20to%20reach%20a%20hospital%20for%20evacuation%3F","correct_answer":"No%20Mercy","incorrect_answers":["Subway%20Sprint","Hospital%20Havoc","Blood%20Harvest"]},{"category":"History","type":"multiple","difficulty":"hard","question":"What%20was%20the%20last%20colony%20the%20UK%20ceded%20marking%20the%20end%20of%20the%20British%20Empire%3F","correct_answer":"Hong%20Kong","incorrect_answers":["India","Australia","Ireland"]}]')},45:function(e,t,a){"use strict";a.r(t);var r=a(0),n=a.n(r),o=a(10),i=a.n(o),c=a(23),s=a(6),l=a(64),u=a(67),d=a(8),m=a(66),h=a(68),y=a(39),p=Object(l.a)({answers:{display:"flex",justifyContent:"space-between",maginTop:"30px",marginBottom:"30px",flexWrap:"wrap",minWidth:"20%"},buttons:{marginBottom:"30px","&:hover":{background:"black",color:"white"}}});function f(e){var t=e.answers,a=e.checkAnswer,r=p();return n.a.createElement("div",{className:r.answers},t&&t.map((function(e){return n.a.createElement(u.a,{variant:"contained",onClick:function(){return a(e)},key:e,className:r.buttons},decodeURIComponent(e))})))}var g=Object(l.a)({container:{border:"2px solid grey",padding:"8px",paddingTop:0,margin:"8px",minHeight:"85vh"},heading:{fontSize:"35px",fontWeight:"bold",marginBottom:"8px"},subHeading:{fontSize:"15px"},result:{display:"flex",justifyContent:"center",alignItems:"center",fontSize:"30px",marginBottom:"20px"},score:{display:"flex",justifyContent:"space-between",padding:"8px"},pogress1:{backgroundColor:"#000000"},progress2:{backgroundColor:"#717171"},progress3:{backgroundColor:"#d2d2d2"},progress:{display:"flex",border:"1px solid black",borderRadius:"8px "}}),w=Object(d.a)({root:{height:15,backgroundColor:"#fff"},bar:{borderRadius:20,backgroundColor:"#a9aaa9"}})(m.a);var b=function(){var e,t=g(),a=Object(r.useState)(0),o=Object(s.a)(a,2),i=o[0],l=o[1],d=Object(r.useState)(y[i].question),m=Object(s.a)(d,2),p=m[0],b=m[1],_=Object(r.useState)([].concat(Object(c.a)(y[i].incorrect_answers),[y[i].correct_answer])),E=Object(s.a)(_,2),v=E[0],C=E[1],S=Object(r.useState)(y[i].category),x=Object(s.a)(S,2),j=x[0],O=x[1],k=Object(r.useState)(y[i].difficulty),q=Object(s.a)(k,2),A=q[0],H=q[1],W=Object(r.useState)(y[i].type),F=Object(s.a)(W,2),B=F[0],N=F[1],M=Object(r.useState)(!1),T=Object(s.a)(M,2),G=T[0],D=T[1],I=Object(r.useState)(0),R=Object(s.a)(I,2),K=R[0],J=R[1],z=Object(r.useState)(0),L=Object(s.a)(z,2),P=L[0],U=L[1],V=Object(r.useState)(!1),Q=Object(s.a)(V,2),X=Q[0],Y=Q[1],Z=Object(r.useState)(!1),$=Object(s.a)(Z,2),ee=$[0],te=$[1];Object(r.useEffect)((function(){}),[]),e="easy"===A?n.a.createElement(h.a,{name:"pristine",value:1,max:3}):"hard"===A?n.a.createElement(h.a,{name:"pristine",value:3,max:3}):n.a.createElement(h.a,{name:"pristine",value:2,max:3});var ae,re=n.a.createElement("div",{className:t.result}," ",X?"Correct!":"Sorry!"),ne=K/y.length*100;ae=0===i?0:K/(K+P)*100;var oe=(K+(y.length-(K+P)))/y.length*100;return console.log(ne,ae,oe,K,P),n.a.createElement("div",{className:t.container},n.a.createElement(w,{variant:"determinate",color:"secondary",value:(i+1)/y.length*100}),n.a.createElement("div",{className:t.heading},"Question ",i+1," of ",y.length),n.a.createElement("span",{className:t.subHeading},decodeURIComponent(j)),n.a.createElement("div",null,e),n.a.createElement("h4",null,decodeURIComponent(p)),n.a.createElement(f,{answers:v,checkAnswer:function(e){X||("multiple"===B?v[3]===e?(J(K+1),Y(!0),D(!0),te(!0)):(U(P+1),te(!0),D(!0),Y(!1)):"boolean"===B&&(v[1]===e?(J(K+1),Y(!0),D(!0),te(!0)):(U(P+1),te(!0),D(!0),Y(!1))))}}),G&&re,ee&&n.a.createElement("div",{className:t.result},n.a.createElement(u.a,{variant:"contained",onClick:function(){return function(){if(i+1===y.length)l(0);else{var e=i+1;l(i+1),b(y[e].question),C([].concat(Object(c.a)(y[e].incorrect_answers),[y[e].correct_answer])),N(y[e].type),O(y[e].category),H(y[e].difficulty),Y(!1),D(!1),te(!1)}}()}},"Next Question")),n.a.createElement("div",{className:t.score},n.a.createElement("div",null,"Score :",ae,"% "),n.a.createElement("div",null,"Max Score : ",oe," % ")),n.a.createElement("div",{className:t.progress},n.a.createElement("div",{style:{width:" ".concat(ne,"%"),backgroundColor:"#000",height:"20px"}}),n.a.createElement("div",{style:{width:"".concat(ae-ne,"%"),backgroundColor:"#717171",height:"20px"}}),n.a.createElement("div",{style:{width:"".concat(oe-ae,"%"),backgroundColor:"#d2d2d2",height:"20px"}})))};a(44);i.a.render(n.a.createElement(n.a.StrictMode,null,n.a.createElement(b,null)),document.getElementById("root"))}},[[34,1,2]]]);
//# sourceMappingURL=main.878d2179.chunk.js.map